There we go.
There's a call for people coming in now as well, so let them come in as well.
Hello.
Sammy, did we lose you for a sec?
My laptop, like literally hates.
Zoom.
Oh, yeah.
I've gone back on my phone.
So, yeah, it's fine.
No worries.
Oh, hey, Rachel.
I didn't realise there's that rating as well.
Hey.
Okay, Sammy, I shall hand over to you to lovely ladies.
For our manifestation master class.
So thank you so much to both of you for doing this.
We really appreciate it.
You know that we love all things manifestations.
I'm really excited about this.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Off you go.
Sorry, one second, I'm just getting my screen.
I can't see the screen that you thought.
Okay.
Do you not add the call?
Oh, no, I'll put it, I'll put it, I'll put it.
Okay.
Kat, do you want me to speak first?
Yeah.
You know.
I'm sure everybody knows you, Sammy.
I'm sure you're all right.
I want to read this so for people to be careful when they speak so according to
quantum physics,
a particle vibration from your sound box when you speak can affect a molecule
inside a star
at the edge of the universe instantly.
I read this year of a day cap.
Amazing.
Yeah, this is what is known as a quantum entanglement.
The greatest illusions of the universe is the illusion of separation.
Do not say your voice, your voice carries no way.
Your words are being absorbed by the edge of the infinity.
Might you create as you speak.
So be careful because, you know, like you said, oh, my life is this, my life is
that.
Yeah, your life is going to be whatever you say.
Good or bad?
I always say to people that I, for years, when I was training, because it was
so hard to
train to be as a psych therapist.
There's so many things you have to go through and with kids and working and
everything as well.
Like before, at the beginning of my training, I always used to say I'm a psych
therapist.
If people asked me who they didn't know me, I'd be like, yeah, I'm a psych
I wasn't.
I was nowhere near.
I was not even a counselor, which is like the beat you have to get to first.
But I just said it so many times.
I just like to believe it.
I just felt like it was true.
And then, yeah, like years later, it was true.
But I just really, that's the first time that I'd ever like put myself out
there and ever
like proclaimed to be something ever.
Because I'd really like was so sort of would never have done that.
And yeah, I just felt like I invited it in before it happened.
I did this with this house.
I was like, I knew that I had an opportunity to have this house and I wanted it
so bad.
So everyone that I spoke to, even my closest, closest friends.
I've been friends since like the beginning of time.
I said, Oh my God, I've got this house.
I'm waiting for a date to move in.
Like that's what I said.
I literally believed it so much that it happened, you know, like I was starting
to buy stuff for
the house before I'd even been told yes or no.
And I was like, I know I've got it, I know I have, I know it's mine.
And to friends and stuff, I say, yeah, I'm waiting on a date to move in.
I can't wait to move into my new house.
And I hadn't even been told yes or no yet.
But I just believed it so much.
And that's where writing, I think, because it was text messages.
Like if you, if you write a text and you're like, yeah, I've got this dream
house.
And I'm just waiting for my date to move in.
I think that's so important, like just writing it down as well.
But that's just my way of manifesting, I think maybe.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm going to try and play this video.
Hopefully it's going to play.
I did allow the audio.
So hopefully you'll have a wee way of doing that.
I was hoping to work on it.
Let me know if you can hear it.
I think there's only, I think there's only one or two slides left after this.
So we are getting people to end now.
This is about seven minutes long.
So maybe I'll stop it a bit short, but I might play the whole thing.
Because I think it's, it's really good.
So let me know if you can hear it.
Thank you.
[applause]
Hear it.
[giggling]
Hi.
[applause]
Good evening.
I want you to turn to the person next to you.
I want you to look him in the eye and introduce yourself as a genius.
Let's begin.
[laughter]
Now geniuses.
So happy to be with you this evening.
I have a few questions for you before we begin.
How many people in this audience actually believe in the idea that the way you
think has some
effect on your life, that your thoughts create your life?
You believe that, yes?
So how many people here actually woke up this morning and consciously created a
future?
You know, the biggest reason why people don't do it is because you don't really
believe
it's true.
You see, if you knew on a gut level that it was absolutely true, would you ever
miss a
day?
Come on.
And would you ever let any thought slip by your awareness that you didn't want
to experience?
So your brain, according to neuroscience, is organised to reflect everything
you know in
your life.
Your brain is a record of your environment.
It's a record, an artifact of your past.
So if you believe this then, then does your environment control your thinking?
Or does your thinking control your environment?
So if you wake up in the morning and you get out of bed on the same exact side
as you did
the day before, you shut the alarm clock off with the same finger, you slip
into your
favourite slippers, you shuffle into the bathroom and you use the toilet like
you always do.
Then you walk over to the mirror and you look at yourself to remember who you
are.
Then you get into the shower and you wash yourself in the same routine way.
Then you groom yourself to look like everybody expects you to look.
Then you go downstairs and you drink coffee out of your favourite mug.
Then you drive the work the same way as you did the day before.
You see the same people that push the same emotional buttons.
You do the exact thing that you know how to do and you memorize and can do so
well that
you're an expert at. Then you hurry up and rush home so you can
hurry up and check your emails so you can hurry up and go to bed so you can
hurry up and do it all over again.
Now here's my question, did your brain change at all that day?
We could say that you were thinking the same thoughts, performing the same
actions
that create the same experiences that produce the same emotions but secretly
expecting something to change in your life.
Would you agree? So then, as the environment turns on
different circuits in your brain, you begin to think equal to your environment.
As you see the same people and go to the same places and do the same things at
the same time,
it's the external environment that's turning on different circuits in your
brain
causing you to think equal to everything that you know.
As long as you think equal to everything that's familiar and known to you,
what do you keep creating more of? The same life.
Now the quantum law is still applying to you. You're just thinking equal to
everything that you know and you keep creating more of the same.
To change, to truly change, is to think greater than your environment.
And every great person in history knew this.
Whether it was William Wallace or Mahatma Gandhi or Martin Luther King
or Queen Elizabeth I or Joan of Arc, they all had a vision.
They all had an idea, couldn't see it, couldn't smell it, couldn't taste it,
couldn't feel it.
But it was alive in their mind.
It was so alive in their mind that they began to live as if that reality was
actually happening now.
So can you believe in a future that you can't see your experience with your
senses yet?
But you've thought about enough times in your mind
that your brain is literally changed to look like the event has already
happened.
Neuroscience says it's absolutely possible.
Now your personality, your personality creates your personal reality.
That's it. It's that simple.
And your personality is made up of how you think, how you act, and how you feel
.
So the present personality who's sitting here today, you,
has created the present personal reality called your life.
Would you agree?
Would you also agree then if you wanted to create a new personal reality
that on a fundamental level you would have to change the thoughts that you're
thinking,
the behaviours and habits that you're demonstrating,
and the emotions that you've memorized that's become part of your identity.
And most of you, you hear me ladies?
Yeah, I think it was almost towards the end then.
So I think it's probably enough for the net because I don't want those running
too far over time.
But I hope you enjoyed that.
And there is so much on just that one person, like Jo to Spencer.
I know Kat, you love him.
I had just read for the second time one of his books because becoming
supernatural.
And also if you'd recommend me that book.
Oh my God, it is incredible. Like it's just incredible.
Like if you want to know all the science,
but then learn about all different people who've completely changed their lives
.
And yeah, it's just full of science and full of stories and full of like
information about how you can do it.
And yeah, I really was inspired by that book.
And so I would definitely recommend it.
Okay, second person.
Yes, you should do it. You get it on Audible, then you can just listen to it.
So I do, I don't watch TV or anything. I just listen to books on Audible and
stuff that inspires me.
And that book is amazing. It's amazing. I'm like re-listening to it again now.
And definitely just like doing an audiobook or actually looking into it now.
As you should. Yeah.
So to summarize some of Sammy's tips, Sammy's top tips and what works for us.
I think I added a couple of onto this is why I put us.
So the vision and the gratitude book that Sammy was talking about before that
she does by herself.
You know, gratitude things and pictures and everything, journaling and spelling
, vision boards, which is something we've done in our calls before haven't we
made vision boards.
Speaking, spelling, acting as if I'm already the person who's received what I
want, like you said before.
So not recycling the same thoughts and the same things that you say to people
and the same actions, same habits every single day, like, you know, stopping
that and creating new ones.
And getting specific about your goals, like Sammy, I think that's one thing you
've done so well is get so specific about what you've wanted.
And to manifest, you have to be specific about what you want, don't you have to
get it.
Because then it's a constant sign.
And then it's like a, let's say, sometimes we, we can make the mistake that we
say, oh yeah, I want the house with it.
I want a house with red a door. And then you see a house that is almost the
same as you want and you are like, well, but the door is blue. Well, I will be
okay with it. Yeah, I don't mind.
And then the law of attraction is already trying to find you the house with
like a with a red door that is aligned to you that everything is going to be
like, not effortless, but it's going to be easy.
And everything aligns for you to like, okay, there is the house. And then when
you change it well, but she said now that it cannot be like that it's like a,
it's like your personal system like, okay, no, we can do something else.
And then you just start reorganizing again to find something else. So that's
why, like what you said and Sammy said they have to be very specific and then
don't change and just let it be.
Sorry girls, I've had to tell my camera off because my daughter's still awake
so I'm just wondering around with my earphones in.
She's, she just doesn't sleep.
There's no manifesting that's going to make us sleep either.
You know, like you were saying about being specific and about where you want to
live so my entire life.
Well, like my adult life. I live in a village called Borton under bleen and I
've always, always wanted to live here like always, I don't know why I just
always have it's just like a really cute little village.
And I've wanted to live here since I was about 19.
So when I wrote my, I love my house and it's important under bleen.
That's what I wrote and I will show you girls tomorrow that I then crossed it
out and wrote her and he'll because this house comes under her and he'll
actually, I live in born under bleen.
And it's just like, it's that like don't confuse the universe but like, because
there's two villages and they're right next to each other.
That's what I wrote intentionally. That's what I was thinking the entire time.
And like, you know, you're like, Oh my God, I live in the village. I've wanted
to live in since I was 19 years old like that's so powerful and so amazing.
Like, I can't tell you enough how much this actually works.
If you, you really like, get into it and believe it and practice what what we
're saying and I'm probably a bit higgledy pickledy because that's just the way
I am.
But yeah, like if you, if you can dream it, you can do it and you can live it.
Like dream please receive. That's what I always say.
And a couple of the other things. So one thing that is in this book becoming
supernatural is about creating a mind movie.
So, George and I created one at the moment, which is a bit of one I'm going to
add to it.
So it's like, it's like a vision board, but a movie, like, so a real basically
making a real with music that you really resonate with.
I need to add music hours, but with the things that you want as if you've
already got them and like dream big, like think big about the things that you
want.
So like pictures or videos of the things you want or whatever put together into
a mind movie that you can use that you can start to associate with the music
that you put with it.
So even when you listen to the song, you don't even have to watch the movie
anymore.
You don't even have to watch the little clip. You can just listen to this song
and have this association and it keeps your focus and attention on the things
you want.
And so that's, that's one thing.
And practising segment intending. So that's another manifestation tip.
And that is that one is Abraham Hicks, I think.
And it's about staying intentional in your day, because a lot of the time we
switch off or we're recycling 90% of the same thoughts and actions like you
saying in the video.
And so we get the same results all the time.
But if you put your day into sections, even like this hour.
So this hour, I am going to go on cam and I'm going to be the best that I can
be. I'm going to be so sexy. I'm going to focus. I'm going to draw people in.
I'm going to have got these stories. I'm going to tell people it's going to be
amazing.
And you literally focus on that one hour that is it. You don't think ahead when
you notice your thoughts going to the what you're going to have for dinner or
like what you did yesterday.
No, draw it back. My focus, my attention is on this segment right now. And even
if it's like, even if it's really hard to stay present and draw, you know, keep
your focus, just doing it for 10 minutes.
Just be like, you know, I'm going to get dressed and I'm going to do it in the
most sensual and connected way to myself. I'm not going to think about what's
next.
I'm not going to think about one, you know, putting my makeup on, which is the
next step. Like, I'm literally going to do this one thing. So like segment
intended is something that helps you to practise becoming present in your life,
rather than doing everything on autopilot, which is what we usually do, which
is why we don't notice opportunities and work towards our goals and all the
rest of it.
So that's one thing. And I guess that kind of goes hand in hand with noticing
recycled thoughts and old habits. So, you know, it's the same as the tabs thing
like closing over the tabs, because if we're thinking the same thoughts every
day.
Oh my God, you know, I think a little bit that and like, well, my boyfriend's
doing this or whatever, like, I've got to do this and I haven't got time like
it's the same thoughts day after day after day so noticing those recycled
thoughts and dealing with them shutting them off replacing them.
And lastly, releasing unworthiness because, yeah, we can't have any of this
stuff if we don't believe that we deserve it.
And obviously imposter syndrome's a big thing and even even to even to ask for
things, even to think that you're worthy to receive things. I know I didn't do
that for a long time, because I had had never received things in life.
So, yeah, it's a habit to break it, that unworthiness, isn't it? And to
actually ask, you know.
And if anyone is struggling with this, please, please, please contact me
privately, and I will talk to you, you know, like between us of how to try and
get over this because it's something that really massively stops us, especially
as women, all of the fucking time and it pisses me off.
So, let's just, you know, like anyone who needs a little bit of help, a little
bit of guidance for this, please don't hesitate to contact me.
Yeah, there is, there is one thing that I put into practice when I, when I have
manifest things, that despite of the situation, despite of everything, just
take yourself back when you used to be a little girl, and you used to maybe
wait for Christmas to write down a letter to Santa.
And you used to believe like, well, how is this Santa is here, and you used to
be like, okay, I want a list of like toys or whatever and then you write them
down, and you knew from your heart some way somehow the things were going to be
under the tree.
Like, you want to, I think I think I think though that's easy for us to say
because some people did write the list and didn't always as a little girl get
what they wanted today I think that sometimes we need to remember, like, I don
't want me, so I love you so much, but I did it, you know, like some people.
I know using that as an example, but some people that would that might be like
a little bit, they did write the list and they didn't always get what they
wanted under the tree.
Checking into that playfulness, and that like childlike thing is maybe a thing
so because I would never have even written the list because I didn't have
family or like toys or anything Christmas, but I can remember being a kid and
lighting in bed and like imagining and dreaming about all the lovely things I
could have.
I'm playing playing as well like I've just been to Disney and honestly like I'm
a little bit of one of the madards like oh god it's going to be like horrendous
so there's going to be crowd just going to be people everywhere there's going
to be kids screaming in my ears, and I loved it so much I was in a maze the
Alice in Wonderland maze and I was like I'm healing by the child right about
now because I have just been taken back to being like.
Seven and like running around like oh my god this is so great you know like not
that ever went to Disney as a kid but I just was so playful and I just let go
of being an adult for two days and it was amazing I was just a child again I
loved it.
Yeah it's basically that like come back to the feeling of like being just worry
less where you are like not even I wasn't reliving like a childhood memory I
was just being a kid again like you know like that like whole.
Watching the one of your favourite Disney films or whatever fantasy film or
whatever as a kid like I'm just sort of running around doing whatever you want
it that's how I felt.
And what we said Sammy like I didn't have that careless time as kid you know I
didn't have times that were like safe and careless and carefree.
It worked so much harder to get to that place of gratitude before things have
happened and so much.
Of course yeah manifestation but it's possible absolutely possible and even
more simple and amazing and abundant when you when you haven't experienced
those things before so.
Yeah it's still possible.
And I think we you know like as because I never been to Disney I think straight
away like that barrier was that even if someone who knows what that they're
doing it is like.
Oh I won't like it it'll be busy they'll be cute every screaming kids like
straight away I'd like put that like kind of weird barrier up because I think I
was a bit like.
I don't even know how to explain it and then as soon as I got there I was like
stop being a dick edge you know like barrier down and I don't really enjoyed
myself and my.
And enjoyed the whole experience and I loved it and it was so amazing and I'm
so grateful for this entire community because without you thought I would never
be able to do this I would never have been able to afford it anything like that
you know like it's so amazing.
But yeah sometimes you just you do it as like a.
We were programmed to protect ourselves aren't we from harmful like memories or
we live in something that wasn't that great for us as kids or whatever so I don
't know sometimes just letting go of it.
And can be okay but obviously I'm you know I know sometimes it can't be as well
but yeah.
And finally girls to finish us off to finish up the call thank you so much to
both of you and Sammy you know all the.
Sorry I've been blaring on.
But it's so hard to like be specific about this kind of thing me and cut
briefly spoke before the call and even then we've got two minutes.
It's really hard to get it into one sort of cool isn't it.
Yeah, there's so much this experience.
Also passionate about it as well.
So long.
Yeah so personal like you know even I know she's not in the court the moment
but her goal setting that first goal setting for me was just absolutely life
changing.
So to sort of see us out.
And hats please tell us about like doing and you know everything.
I'm going to grab my phone so basically.
To get more into detail with this.
I really spoke to Sammy. Sammy probably will join me.
We will discuss this but basically 47 matter what I want to do for you girls.
It's like help you to set up your mum okay based on the moon faces.
Okay following a full moon following the new moon following the last quarter
and the first quarter to.
So where our we are going to align our energies towards like the the moon to
get the best of it.
Okay, like I said sometimes we can get through loads of emotions through the
month which I don't really get it.
But I can help you to like at certain things into your life to do it through
the week for you to get the most of the month and manifest like the things you
want or just get you in that mindset where you start resonating
with that internal energy and you start like a stereo rising I think that's a
word.
Yeah I stereo rising and your your your inner feelings out.
So I'm going to pass a on the what's up group the calendar.
So you girls know a little bit what to expect but basically our first meeting
will be on the seventh of December, which is the full moon.
So we are going to do some rituals things that you can do at home and it's
always on the self love.
And for you to put in practice and let out that which person that we all have
inside a base on our intuition.
So we all have intuition. Some people think like a well mine is very developed,
mine is not as much, but we are going to put into practice and use more our
intuition to bring a manifest just following our heart.
So, and I want to like whoever wants to join us on those calls. Please just
come and join us. You won't regret it because, like I said to rail, the same
but it's a very busy month where you got all like a yeah yeah I'm happy you
know it's a happy month for some people
it's not very happy for some other part is a busy month. So and keep your mind
busy. So that's I like to do one month. So then we continue in January to set
up your goals for next year.
Because January is is when they come down start and most people will need it so
whoever wants to join us from from January from December is more than welcome
to come.
Yeah, like I said to Europe. And we are going to do things for self love like
no stress and it's going to be very interactive, like probably maybe one day I
will be like a let's all put the cameras on it doesn't matter how you look.
Let's just do something that is for you while we all do it together because I
believe like guys going to be more like a ceremony where all our energies will
align to help all of us to connect and resonate in the same energy.
So we create what we want. So anybody is welcome to do it, Sami and I can't
have only said like when women get especially women get together and allowing
their energies, the powerful things we can do is mind blowing.
I was going to say, because not only is it would do we have personal experience
of that in the group. And, and, but we also there is scientific proof now that
when people get together in groups and raise their vibrational frequency
together
and they test it with these monitors the brain scans and stuff that they can
literally lower the percent lower the percentage of the crime rate within a
certain mile radius in the place that they do this gathering is getting
together of like
3,000 people who are doing this, like heart brain coherence meditation and then
bring their brain scans and seeing that they literally change the frequency of
the area and then the crime comes down like together we're so powerful.
Yes, I mean, I believe like the world should be wrong by us, because our
empathy levels are so high, our, you know that motherly that we all carry is
just like something that the world will be like from by us.
Anyway, however, something that I just want you guys to prepare to just be let
let that crazy person out where we are going to probably be chanting together
just resonating so we bring the best energy out of us.
And it's something that is crazy and many people doesn't really know that. But
the first chamens that is like a priest like a spiritual breeze. They were
females.
They were females because we have that intuition we are connected to earth. We
can, we can bring every sense is everything we are so perceptive.
So, and I want you to all of you used that on your advantage for, for your
things that you want to achieve so I'm pretty sure that you will, you can take
the most out of this.
And you can create whatever you want from this plus is something that it will
be just a month to start with. And then if you want to carry on next month, it
will just bring the best out of you.
And I said to something we are planning to put things together where you are
going to feel like, oh my God, I'm looking forward to this. And then we said,
didn't we, that we'd, you know, if people are interested, we'd offer like a
reading at the start of your journey.
Yeah, one to one then like, what's it called, I don't know if the word now to
use but you know like one to one.
If you feel like you want to actually learn more when I have your own question,
and maybe you don't want to, you don't feel like I just want to expose
everything here because sometimes in some meetings can be a little bit like I
just don't want to say anything.
You can read how, and we can be just, you know, like very like less. Okay, come
on.
And then after a month, isn't it great to then have another reading and see the
difference between the first reading and then like the second reading and what
you've, you know how that's changed and I'm such a believer in card readings
and how amazing they are.
So yeah. And I'm also someone who can't sit still for longer than an hour. That
's one just like wandering around.
I don't mind admitting it. I cannot sit still any longer girl.
Yeah, it's been such a lovely call. And yeah, I'm so grateful to you both for
your just for energy and for your time and attention. Thank you so much
everyone.
Yeah, thank you for everyone for coming and keeping an eye out on the group,
you know, for the support that cat and Sammy are going to be offering for free,
you know, for you to, you know, maybe make a list tonight or tomorrow.
What you're planning to manifest what you want.
And you know these ladies will help you to achieve it. So yeah, I hope that
will all stay in touch anyway, and will tell us about it in the group and then.
Yeah, we'll see you. So the more it's a new day tomorrow you will get all the
info and then we will go from there.
Yes, amazing. Thank you.
Thank you.
Also great tool. I've not seen you for ages. And Jesse, I know you've not felt
well at all today.
So I was expecting to see your beautiful faces. I don't love you both so much.
I just wanted to say something quite interesting that I've been, I've been
doing a lot of research about the beginning of patriarchy and the witch hunts
and the shift.
So I found very, very interesting about what you're saying about women coming
together is that, like, one of the reasons why there was actually the witch
trials was because women.
When we keep mice away, women kept cuts to keep mice away.
No, no, so what is the reason why the witch trial started was because women
used to congregate together and at the start of like when the patriarchy was
really being enforced, condemning women who crowded together was like an easy
way for them to say that they were getting together
and doing like witchy stuff, which often wasn't the case, but it was separating
women that through fear and things like that.
No, I just really quickly interrupt you, Jesse. If you look back further
through that, it's because they thought with me more witches because they used
to literally keep cats, cats keep rats away and sweep their houses with brooms
to keep them clean.
And then they all got together and was like, oh, this is how you keep your
house clean. And then men didn't like it. They were like, fuck them, they're
like doing witches here.
There was a few things, it was also going to work actually the first healers.
And this was before the idea of the doctors came in and natural healers who are
women threatened that practice as well.
But anyway, one thing that's really quite powerful is like when women do come
together like that, we are also like threatening the patriarchy because that's
one of the first tools that were used to shift women towards individualism and
break them up.
So it's also kind of like an active protest when women come together and
congregate. Absolutely.
And I think it's so rooted in history and separating women has had such drastic
effect on like where we are now. So it's quite a cool way to look at activism
really.
Anyway, yeah, I think, I think also because I'm our female side, obviously
everybody has their female on the masculine, but our female side, let us follow
, which males, they tend to be, I want to be the head.
So for us to have a leader and lots of people following is quite easy and
understanding and we support each other, which males, they are not as much like
that sometime.
And probably they say, like you said, they see us as a proper thread because we
are.
Because without, without, you know, like so much in the media, we're made to
feel like, you know, you're not good enough or this person's better looking or
whatever, like, I think it's constantly in our faces to be against each other.
Yeah, rather than together, and actually, especially like a community like this
is so bloody important to all stick together. And we've already been, people
have tried to break us up by deleting our videos off of YouTube and stuff like
that, because it's like, Oh God, this is scary.
There's like a hundred women that are all going to stick together. And, you
know, like, change something because we have more boys because we will change
things.
And, you know, it's not, and it's like, I even cringe when I hear about like
male and females like we are this, they are that I think no let's step away
from these stories because we are not defined by our gender we're not defined
by this separation
and the splitting. We all have the masculine and feminine every single
individual on this earth. And there's more than two categories. And so let's
just like Jess said I think it's an, it isn't an act of, you know, it is
activism, isn't it, to come together in these faces.
It's the narrative as well. It's an narrative that was told, isn't it?
It's making like a matriarchal spaces, you know, is so cool.
But so hard to change, you know, like, even in my family who I love so much, my
mum always has to be, Oh, you should have been a boy, or boys do this and girls
do this, you know, like, it's just so the narrative or everything around us,
girls are this boys are that, you know, like, it's so hard to step away from.
It's part of the programming that is keeping us in our place but you can step
outside of that I feel like I have done that as much as it's humanly possible,
and it's brought me a lot of opportunities and, you know, made me sit in a lot
of rooms I wouldn't have thought I could have.
Yeah, we need to, we need to release it from ourselves and just deal with the,
you know, what we face in other people.
And also just being present because when you present, you can be more conscious
of subliminal messaging, like, I don't know if you saw it in the chat, like, I
was thinking today, like, fancied watching like a Christmas film, but I was
like, I don't actually think there's one Christmas film that I'm going to watch
and not going to make me feel like shit.
Because it's all highlighting, like, loneliness, dependence on family, do you
know what I mean, things that, for me, somebody who's an immigrant that doesn't
have a family here or a partner, it's going to watch that, I feel like crap, do
you know what I mean?
But when you are, when you are more conscious of subliminal messaging, you can
also see things and then be like, oh, I'm not going to let this make me feel
crap, you don't have to, like, just reject everything, but you can also be
aware of what's like actually happening
and then you can choose to be like, nah, I'm just missing this, you know?
Like, I live so much of my life with hero worship in them, and thinking that
everything they did or said was right and everything they told me that I was
doing wrong was wrong, I think it's something I was doing right was right.
Once I stepped out of that, my God, my life changed so much, you know, like, so
much.
I think that maybe we need another call, I think we need another call on this
thing, because there's so much more and it's a separate thing, isn't it really,
like, what it means to be a woman and what it means to be.
Yeah, I think you could do it quite a cool call about subliminal messaging and
society, because it's like when you know what you can act, you can actually
dissect it more and then, like I said, it makes you feel less shitty.
Do you know what she would do as well, have a December social chat, but we
could all just join in, get a drink, wander around if you like me, can't keep
still for five minutes, and just have a little get together and say what's on
our minds and just like without any pressure or structure.
Yeah, let's do that, let's have their social, where we can just, yeah, where we
can talk about some of this.
Not just I've tried to be structured tonight, I feel like I've just completely
gone away from it a lot of the time, so it's been quite nice to just have like
a little, I'm going to say what they want to say and like it was social catch
up, especially December as well when people do feel like she at all feel really
great as well.
No, like all get together and with our mixed emotions and just, yeah, maybe
that's what our monthly mental health call can be next time just like a, like a
women circle, just like an open space, maybe we should do that next time.
Yeah, that'd be nice. Do you reckon? Yes, let's do it ladies. Yeah, right, I am
off to the weekend and hopefully get on camera a little bit and, yeah, get
sorted.
And so nice, honestly, I feel charged, so thank you. And anyone who does want
any extra, you know, like, wants to talk about a little bit more about crystals
years, I haven't even mentioned essential oils or anything like that, like any
stuff they want to know can message me, absolutely no problem.
Yeah, and everyone's saying, you know, how much they love the call, really
loved it, really needs it. Thank you felt right, really needs to be in this
space. Thank you so much ladies. So yeah, lots of thank you from everyone. So
thank you ladies.
Thank you. Yes, we shall all catch up on June.
Have a lovely evening ladies.
Bye bye girl. Thank you.
Bye everyone.
Bye.